Finding Aid for the Alice Greenfield McGrath Papers LSC.1490
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 10. Memorial ephemera., 2009
  - University of California at Los Angeles - digital images for memorial., 2009 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Includes 1 DVD with scanned images that were used in the slide show presentation.
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Digital materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - Memorial album., 2009 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Album containing remembrances of Alice McGrath. Authors include: Martin Hird, Arthur Gilbert, Greg Totten, Amanda Irma Perez, and Rene Rodriguez.